SANDRA POULET

Mobile: +971-50-811-1254 Email: lafortunesandra@gmail.com

FINANCIAL SECTOR PROFESSIONAL

A top-performing professional in the financial sector with the ability to seamlessly juggle multiple responsibilities while still providing clear leadership, instruction, and internal support.

A big picture thinker with years of corporate-level experience in hedge funds and operational management. Combines advanced market knowledge, computational, and analysis skills with a positive, personable, and professional attitude.

Multi-lingual, with the ability to lead and motivate large multi-ethnic teams, and a great problem solver with the ability to anticipate and find resolutions to future demands.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Hedge Fund Administration. **Operations**
- Internal Reporting & Operational **Procedures**
- Strategic Planning/Analysis
- Team building & team leading
- Risk Management Risk Analysis
- **Business Development**
- Advanced Microsoft Office Skills
- Project Management, IT improvements
- Effective communication
- **VBA & Bloomberg**
- Fluent English, French (native), and Spanish

KEY SKILLS ASSESSMENT

- Providing clear oversight and leadership to team members while publicly representing an organization's goals and objectives to external stakeholders.
- Coordinating projects/assignments simultaneously and completing tasks accurately on a timely basis
- Strongly committed, what enables me to find solutions in order to improve the business, work flows
- Sensitivity to regulatory as well as risk and control matters

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MATERNITY LEAVE 2014 - 2016

NEXAM/UBP. PARIS. FRANCE **HEAD OF MIDDLE OFFICE**

IN 2010. NEXAM BOUGHT OUT ALLIANZ GLOBAL INVESTORS.

IN 2013, NEXAM WAS PURCHASED BY L'UNION BANCAIRE PRIVÉE (UBP).

- Supervised the valuation of 16 alternative funds of funds (Ucits and non-Ucits funds). [10Bn AUM in 2007]
- Responsible for all aspects and components of NexAM's daily, weekly and/or monthly NAV calculations.
- Managed the day-to- day euro/dollar treasury and updated the treasury timeframe each day.
- Analyzed and improved internal reportings: weekly estimates, shareholder activities, P&L activity reports.
- Drove performance measures and KPIs
- Supervised secondary market transactions
- Reviewed pricing reports for illiquid or hard to price securities.
- Handled multiple demands and competing priorities
- Accountable for analysis, documentation, testing and delivery of new products or functionalities development managed by the Fund Accounting team
- Improved information flows, professional and friendly relationships between transverse services (risks and analysts teams, client service) and external counterparties.
- Assisted with the preparation of financial statements and audits.
- Effective communication: conveyed clear goals and expectations when involving others in projects; coordinated work efforts with other groups; conducted and led frequent team meetings; provided appropriate direction and clarified roles and responsibilities with team members; brought together new approaches and different perspectives to generate new ideas.
- Promoted a client centric culture across the team

2007 - 2013

Sandra Poulet

Mobile: +971-50-811-1254

Email: lafortunesandra@gmail.com

- Executed on a process of continuous improvement that assesses workflows, processes and procedures on an ongoing basis, ensuring maximum efficiency and quality within the Fund Accounting team
- Built a cohesive team spirit that would foster a clear client service focus, operational efficiency and an error free environment
- Accepted and successfully executed change management while supporting employees through the process.
- Cut costs and handled budget constraints. Managed team reductions and project suspensions.
- Worked under pressure and conformed to tight deadlines.

ALLIANZ GLOBAL INVESTORS FRANCE, PARIS, FRANCE

2003 - 2007

- MUTUAL FUNDS OFFICER
 - Oversaw the funds' daily flows on equities, bonds, and mutual funds.
 - Checked the accuracy of each brokers' confirmations with each trades booked in the system.
 - Managed all the funds' treasuries with daily money markets cash adjustments.
 - Utilized Excel skills to set up new follow-up tools: mutual funds' ratios, brokers ranking and brokerage commissions
 - Participated in the set-up of a new PMS (Omgeo-Global Oasys)
 - Developed an automated positions reconciliation tool and created a new automated treasury management tool (Excel and Business Objects)
 - Actively served on the Sustainable Development Committee from 2005 to 2010.

FUDTHED EVDEDIENCE

FURTHER EXPERIENCE	
UBS PRIVATE BANKING, PARIS, FRANCE EQUITIES TRADING ASSISTANT	2002
LA CIE FINANCIERE E.DE ROTSCHILD, PARIS, FRANCE EQUITIES MIDDLE OFFICE (OFFSHORE FUNDS)	2002
MERRILL LYNCH CAPITAL OFFICE, PARIS, FRANCE DEBT OPERATIONS OFFICER	2001
NATIXIS, PARIS, FRANCE BONDS TREASURY MANAGEMENT OFFICER	2000 - 2001
MOTOROLA TEL-CO, ANTONY, FRANCE CREDIT ANALYST	1997 - 2000
DEDALE, ROISSY, FRANCE ACCOUNTANT	1996 - 1997

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Capital Market Foundations Certificate (612/800) First Finance Institute | United Arab Emirates | 2015

Master of Arts - major International Industry & Finance | Université Paris 13 Nord | France | 1992-1995

A Levels - major Economics | Lycée | Rousseau | France | 1990